FEMINISATION / SISSIFICATION. DEFINITION SISSY
TRAINING is a process where submissive men learn to take on traditionally female
roles. The submissive, known as sissy, learns ultra-feminine behaviours and performs
feminine activities under the guidance of his dominant partner.
This can range from housekeeping or applying make-up to sexual acts such as body
worship or being anally penetrated. The sexual play comes from power play and or
erotic humiliation. HOW DO I EVEN BEGIN SISSY TRAINING?
If you are brand new to SISSY training, you are probably thinking how do I even begin
to train them? SISSY and findom relationships are built on a deep level of trust
and understanding which can be developed over time.
If you use some or all of the steps in this guide you will be well on your way to
building a relationship with a client who will keep coming back time and time again.
UNDERWEAR Start with underwear, tell them to find or buy some women's lingerie.
A cute pair of panties is a good place to start.
If your client is an experienced SISSY, they are likely to have a full collection
already so ask them what they have and then ask them to dress up for you.
It is good to ask them if they feel like a lady or a slut to establish what level
of humiliation they may like. You can also tell them to wear panties at work and
ask them to get a photo for you as evidence so that they are thinking about you even
away from the call and they'll want to come back and talk to you.
MAKE HIM LOOK PRETTY It's so easy for your SISSY to act feminine when he looks the
part. Nail polish is a good place to start.
Hot pink or bright red painted on his toes are perfect.
Make him wear the nail polish for the whole week, even to work.
It is a great way to assert your dominance over him and keep the humiliation going
even when you're not around. You can also get your client to put makeup on depending
on what they have or what they are willing to buy.
Red lipstick is a great starting point and then make fun of him while he tries to
make himself look beautiful. THE HAIR If the client's hair is long enough, he could
put it in little bunches or get girly clips to put in it.
If he's serious about being a sissy, he probably has a wig.
Get him to brush it in front of you or try to style it prettily for you.
BODY HAIR As well as being pretty, his body should be smooth.
This means no bushy beards, no hairy arms, no hairy legs, chest, back or ass.
Everything off. Of course, this is a lot in one go and depending on their personal
situation it might not be possible. Begin by asking them to begin with their crotch
area since no one sees that. Then strip the chest and back etc.
Building up to the arms and legs if possible.
Act the part. Now it's time for your sissy to walk the walk and talk the talk.
Give them a name. Give your sissy a pretty name or ask them if they already have
one. Having a new name gets them into character.
Old-fashioned etiquette techniques. Walk with a book on his head.
Learn to sit cross legged. Practice speaking in a higher pitched voice.
Swaying hips when he's walking. Seductive body language.
Moan like a woman. Another great tip is to teach them how to be a woman using
old-fashioned etiquette techniques. Get them to place a book on his head and teach him
to walk in high heels if possible. Teach him how to sit cross legged like a lady.
Another idea is to use vocal training techniques to soften his voice or increase
the pitch. You can also get him to practice how to sway his hips when he walks.
Practice seductive body language and moan like a woman during sex.
This stage of sissy training can be made even more fun with punishments and rewards.
Sexualise your sissy. Now it's time to sexualise your sissy.
Orgasm denial and chastity. Lady versus slut.
Blowjob training. And anal play. Dominate your sissy by not allowing him to orgasm.
Tell him that it's not a very lady like thing to do.
You can also deny orgasm over a period of time if chastity training is something
they enjoy. Combining the chastity play with sissification will completely strip
him of his manhood and put his sexual pleasure under your control.
As well as training your sissy to be a lady he should also learn how to be a slut.
This is where the fun begins. You could ask them to put on a slutty webcam show especially
for you. Or get them to pose in sexual positions for example twerking.
Use your imagination. Blowjob training is a great way to feminise them.
Have them give a dildo a sensual blowjob or just use his fingers if he doesn't have
one. You can make him watch porn and copy it if he needs help.
As well as giving oral your sissy should be trained to receive penetration.
If he's brand new to anal training, then start with a finger or two before moving
onto a small dildo. Put into practice. Tell
your client to dress up as a female. Transform them into a sissy.
Turn them into a sissy maid. Make them wear a frilly, skimpy uniform and tell them
to perform duties from sexual acts to household chores.
Build a relationship with a sissy. Make him come back every week for more training.
Build your relationship slowly. Get them to complete tasks for you.
Verbal humiliation. Refer to the submissive as a pet, bitch or dog, slave, missy
or poke fun at the submissive's body. Verbal humiliation should always be consensual,
and some clients use a safe word which can be used to stop the interaction if it
goes too far. Hi everyone. I hope these steps gave you a better idea on how to train
your sissy. And also helps you with understanding what type of things these types
of clients like. You can play with other humiliation tactics that are found
on this course as a lot of fetishes cross over and your client may enjoy more than
one kink. With that being said, it's time for you to go and put this into practice.
Good luck and make sure to let us know how you got on.
Bye.